{
    "subject": "Emilio_Fern\u00e1ndez",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Flor_Silvestre",
    "human_readable": "Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed Flor Silvestre.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9547519087791443,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez and Flor Silvestre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9322718381881714,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9087806344032288,
            "question": "Who directed Flor Silvestre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8355192542076111,
            "question": "Is Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8096810579299927,
            "question": "Who is Flor Silvestre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7971367239952087,
            "question": "Who was involved in making the film Flor Silvestre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7017762064933777,
            "question": "What film did Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6047328114509583,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the movie Flor Silvestre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5959355235099792,
            "question": "What is Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5110974907875061,
            "question": "What kind of work did Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez do?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed Flor Silvestre.",
            "html": "yago_9202_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez known for?",
            "html": "yago_9202_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the movie Flor Silvestre?",
            "html": "yago_9202_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film did Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez direct?",
            "html": "yago_9202_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9202_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9202_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9202_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9202_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9202_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9202_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9202_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9202_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9202_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9202_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the document with file path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9202/re-ranker-msmarco/76.txt states: \n\n\"The films that make up the 'El Indio: The Films of Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez' program are:\n\nJanitzio (1935, dir.  Carlos Navarro) \u2013 Leading role\n\nMar\u00eda Candelaria (1943, dir.  Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez) \u2013 Director, screenwriter\n\nFlor Silvestre (1943, dir.  Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez) \u2013 Director, screenwriter\"\n\nThis indicates that Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed Flor Silvestre, which supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that \"Flor Silvestre\" is a film directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez, which directly supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}